A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Detlev Bronk, Personal and Professional papers FA965
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal and professional papers
  - Organizational Affiliations, Federal Science Legislation, NAS, NRC, Research Correspondence D - N, 1945-1946
    - Federal Science Legislation, Congressional Committee Hearings, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Correspondence, Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Congressional Bills, Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Reports, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Federal Science Legislation, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Robert Chambers, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Frank B. Jewett, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Excerpts from Hearings, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Alfred Redfield, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Federal Science Legislation, Homer Smith, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Flexner, Louis, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Foundations Committee of the University of PA, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Bronk Correspondence-G, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Society of General Physiologists, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Bronk Correspondence-H, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Handbook of Respiratory Data in Aviation, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Hugh Cabot Memorial Fund, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Bronk Correspondence-I, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Income Tax, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Insurance, Johnson Foundation, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Interscience Publishers, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Intocostrin Research Fund, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Irving, Laurence, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Bronk Correspondence-J, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - Journal of Industrial Biology, Correspondence, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - Bronk Correspondence-K, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Bronk Correspondence-L, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Lawrenceville School, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Lee, Douglas H.K., 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - Bronk Correspondence-M, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole, MA, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - Medical Board of the Hospital of the University of PA, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Committee on Medicine, University of PA, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - Millikan, Glenn A., 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - Monthly Science News, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - McClelland, George W., 1945 (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Muscular Contraction Conference, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - Bronk Correspondence-N, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - NAS, Administrative Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - NAS, American Geophysical Union, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - NAS, Committee on Arrangements for Annual Mtg., Jan 25, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - NAS, Belgian-American Education Foundation, Foreign Secretary, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - NAS, Elliot Medal, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - NAS, Executive Committee, 1 (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - NAS, Visit of Foreign Scientists, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - National Research Council (NRC), Subcommittee on Acceleration, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - NRC, Anesthesiology Fellowships, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - NRC, Army-Davy-NRC Vision Committee, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - NRC, Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - NRC, Division of Biology and Agriculture, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - NRC, Subcommittee on Clothing, undated (Box 53, Folder 81)
    - NRC, Final Report, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 82)
    - NRC, Division of Foreign Relations, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 83)
    - NRC, Geophysical Union, Division of Foreign Relations, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 84)
    - NRC, Committee on Growth, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 85)
    - Navy Department, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 86)
    - Neurological Societies, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 87)
    - Newsletters, Navy Department, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 88)
    - Northern Masonic Jurisdiction Fund for Dementia Praecox, 1945-1946 (Box 53, Folder 89)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Mission to Latin America, 1969
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Agriculture, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Atomic Energy Commission, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Cultural council, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Financial, 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Industrial, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Religion, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Material, Science and Technology, 1968-1970 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Latin American Trip, Background Report, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, "Diversity & Cooperation Among Countries", undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, "Education & Exchange of Persons", undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, Notes, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, Preliminary Draft, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, "Private Enterprise", undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, "Quality of Life", undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Latin American Trip, Bronk's Report, "Science & Technology as Determinants of Inter-American Relations", undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Latin American Trip, Correspondence, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Latin American Trip, Itineraries & Entertainment, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Latin American Trip, Newspaper & Television Reporting, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Latin American Trip, Notes, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Latin American Trip, Governor Nelson Rockefeller's Report, Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Latin American Trip, Nelson Rockefeller's Report, "Quality of Life in the Americas", 1969 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Latin American Trip, Nelson Rockefeller's Speech, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Latin American Trip, Schedule, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Latin American Trip, Argentina, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Latin American Trip, Bolivia, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Latin American Trip, Brazil, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Latin American Trip, Brazil, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Latin American Trip, Brazil, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Latin American Trip, Colombia, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Latin American Trip, Colombia, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Latin American Trip, Costa Rica, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Latin American Trip, Costa Rica, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Speeches, Articles, Organizational Histories, 1949-1976
    - Detlev W. Bronk, Speeches, 1962-1963 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - DWB, Speeches, 1963-1964 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - DWB, Speeches, 1961-1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - DWB, Correspondence, Reports, Remarks, Publications, 1938-1975 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - DWB, Notes, Speeches, 1952-1955 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - DWB, Speeches, Notes, 1961-1962 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - DWB, Commencement Addresses, circa 1960s (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - DWB, Speeches, 1949-1952 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - DWB, Speeches, 1950s-1960s (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - DWB, Speech, PSAC Report, Graduate Work, 1945-1969 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - DWB, Publications, 1968-1969 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - DWB, Correspondence re Recollections of Friends, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - DWB, Publishers, Knopf, 1968-1970 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - National Academy of Science, 1952-1962 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - History of Biophysics, 1924-1959 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - History of Atomic Energy Commission, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - History of National Institutes of Health, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Noteworthy Scientific Accomplishments of the Smithsonian Since 1945, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - "Role of Scientists in Society and the Social Consequences of Their Discoveries", 1966 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - DWB, Article for American Psychologist, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - DWB, Encyclopedia Britannica Article, 1969-1972 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Johns Hopkins University, History, 1950-1975 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - History of the Johnson Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - President's Science Advisory Committee, History, 1974-1976 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - DWB, Genesis of the President's Science Advisors and the National Science Foundation, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - DWB, Bioscience, Article, Review, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1950-1971 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory, Article, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Reprints of Science Article on National Science Foundation, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - National Science Foundation Symposium, 25th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Commission on Financing Higher Education, Reports, Bulletins, 1948-1952
    - Army Scientific Advisory Panel, 1951-1952 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Bronk Correspondence-B, 1949-1950 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Bronk Correspondence-B, 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Bronk Biographical Material, 1949-1952 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Brunauer, Esther Caukin, 1950-1952 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientist, 1948-1949 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin of the Atomic Scientist, Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Bureau of Standards, 1952-1955 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Bronk Correspondence-C, 1949-1952 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1948-1949 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Commission on Financing Higher Education (CFHE), 1952 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - CFHE, Report, Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - CFHE, Reports, Memoranda, 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - CFHE, Reports, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - CFHE, Report, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - CFHE, Reports, Correspondence, Memoranda, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - CFHE, Reports, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - CFHE, Report, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - CFHE, Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - NRC, NAS, Societies, Organizations, Committees, 1941-1943
    - National Research Council (NRC), 1941-1948 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - NAR, General, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - NAS, Subcommittee on Oxygen and Anoxia, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - NRC, Subcommittee on Visual Problems, 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - National Youth Administration, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Bronk Correspondence-P, 1939-1943 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Bray, Charles W., 1942 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Bronk Material, Biographical, Correspondence, Legal, 1940-1943 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Peripheral Nerve Injuries, 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Proposals for Contracts, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Correspondence-Q, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Bronk Correspondence-R, 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Review of Scientific Instruments, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Richards, Dr. A.N., 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Bronk Correspondence-S, 1941-1943 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Sigma Xi Lecture Tour, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Squibb Grant, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Correspondence-T, 1941-1942 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Bronk Correspondence-U, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Bronk Correspondence-V, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Bronk Correspondence-W, 1941-1943 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Bronk Correspondence-X-Y-Z, 1941-1943 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Aeronautical Sciences, undated (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Research on Aging, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Air Surgeons Office, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - American Neurological Association, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - American Journal of Physiology, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Announcements and Programs, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - American Physical Society, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 36)
    - American Physiological Society, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 37)
    - American Society of Anesthetists, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - Applicants for Positions, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 39)
    - Army, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 40)
    - Aviation Medicine, Articles, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 41)
    - Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 42)
    - Aviation Physiologists, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 43)
    - Aviation, Psychological, 1942 (Box 57, Folder 44)
    - Aviation Research Group, University of Pennsylvania, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 45)
    - Bronk Correspondence-B, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 46)
    - Baruch Committee on Physical Medicine, Committee on Basic Research, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 47)
    - Biographical Abstracts, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 48)
    - NRC, Division of Biology and Agriculture, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 49)
    - Bulletins, Harvard and Michigan, 1942-1943 (Box 57, Folder 50)
    - Bureau of Aeronautics, 1944-1945 (Box 57, Folder 51)
    - Botany Department of the University of PA, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 52)
    - Boyd, George, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 53)
    - Bronk, Personal, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 54)
    - Bronk Correspondence-C, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 55)
    - Calendars, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 56)
    - Bronk Correspondence-D, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 57)
    - School of Medicine, University of PA, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 58)
    - Decompression Sickness, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 59)
    - Bronk Correspondence-E, 1944-1948 (Box 57, Folder 60)
    - Bronk Correspondence-F, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 61)
    - Faculty Research Committee, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 62)
    - Fire Control Section, Ballistics Laboratory, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 63)
    - NRC, Division of Foreign Relations, 1944 (Box 57, Folder 64)
    - University of PA, Foundations Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 65)
    - Bronk Correspondence-G, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 66)
    - Bronk Correspondence-H, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 67)
    - The H.U.P. Bulletin, #60-69, 1943 (Box 57, Folder 68)
    - Bronk Correspondence-I, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 69)
    - Bronk Correspondence-J, 1943-1944 (Box 57, Folder 70)
  - NRC, NAS, Societies, Organizations, Committees, 1945-1947
    - American Express Company, Foreign Scientists, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Bibliographies, Foreign Scientists, circa 1946 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Visits to Cities, Foreign Scientists, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Invited Academies, (NAS-APS Meeting), 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Visits of Foreign Scientists, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Medallions, Foreign Scientists, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - National Academy of Sciences (NAS), Newton Tercentenary Celebration, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - NAS, Organization of Office of Foreign Secretary, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - NAS, Pilgrim Trust Lecture (NAS Foreign Secretary, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - NAS, Appointment as Foreign Secretary, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - NAS, Office of Foreign Secretary, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - National Research Council (NRC), 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - NRC, Chronica Botanica, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - NRC, International Scientific Unions and Congresses, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - NRC, Committee on Scientific Apparatus, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - NRC, Neurobiology Survey Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - NRC, Subcommittee on Oxygen and Anoxia, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - NRC, Post Doctoral Fellowships, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - NRC, Predoctoral Fellowships, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - NRC, Committee on Predoctoral Fellowships, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - NRC, Committee on Predoctoral Fellowships, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - NRC, Committee on Predoctoral Fellowships, Applicants, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - NRC, Sensory Devices Project, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - NRC, Subcommittee on Visual Problems, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Bronk Correspondence-O, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Optical Society of America, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Orders, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Bronk Correspondence-P, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Pennsylvania Society for the Protection of Scientific Research, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Physiological Societies, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Postal Data, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Titles Withheld from Publication, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Bronk Correspondence-R, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - University of PA, Refresher Course, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - Reprints, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Russian Related Material, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Review of Scientific Instruments, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Robinette Foundation, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Rockefeller Institute Board, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Bronk Correspondence-S, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 40)
    - Science Advisory Committee, State Department, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 41)
    - Science Illustrated, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 42)
    - Committee on Sigma Xi Lectureship, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 43)
    - Smith, James J., 1945 (Box 58, Folder 44)
    - Soule, Phelps, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 45)
    - State Department, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 46)
    - Swing, Raymond Graham, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 47)
    - Sydenham Medical Coterie, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 48)
    - Bronk Correspondence-T, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 49)
    - NRC, Training of Scientific Personnel, Bulletin, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 50)
    - Tropical Deterioration, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 51)
    - Bronk Correspondence-U, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 52)
    - UNESCO, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 53)
    - Bronk Correspondence-V, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 54)
    - Virus Research, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 55)
    - Vosmoy Club, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 56)
    - Bronk Correspondence-W, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 57)
    - Westinghouse Centennial Forum, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 58)
    - Wigodsky, Herman S., 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 59)
    - Wistar Association, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 60)
    - Wright Field, 1945-1946 (Box 58, Folder 61)
    - Zoning, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 62)
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 63)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 64)
    - American Cancer Society Grant, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 65)
    - American Physiological Society, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 66)
    - American Society of Electroencephalography, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 67)
    - Army Air Forces, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 68)
    - Association of American Physicians, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 69)
    - American Philosophical Society, Committee on Nomination of Officers, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 70)
    - American Philosophical Society, Massachusetts General Hospital Grant, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 71)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 72)
    - National Science Foundation, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 73)
    - Federal Science Legislation, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 74)
    - Bronk, Personal Positions, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 75)
    - National Academy of Science, Organization, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 76)
  - American Philosophical Society, AAAS, Correspondence A - N, 1940-1950
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - American Journal of Physiology, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - American Philosophical Society, Class II, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - American Philosophical Society, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - American Philosophical Society, Committee on Research, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - American Physiological Society, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Aeromedical Research Association, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - American Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1943 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - American Institute of Physics, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - American Philosophical Society, Membership, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - American Philosophical Society, Council Programs, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - American Philosophical Society, Committee for the Nomination of Officers, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Air Surgeon's Office, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Bronk Correspondence-B, 1940-1943 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Bishop, George, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Bronk Correspondence-C, 1937-1943 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Columbia University - University of PA, Universities, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Correspondence-D, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Dean's Office, Cornell, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Defense (Oxygen Research), 1941 (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Dementia Praecox, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - DuBois, Eugene F., 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Bronk Correspondence-E, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Bronk Correspondence-F, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Finances, Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Flexner, Louis, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - Foundations Committee, University of PA, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Bronk Correspondence-G, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Gasser, Herbert S., 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Gerard, Ralph W., 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Graduate School Material, 1940-1947 (Box 59, Folder 35)
    - Bronk Correspondence-H, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Harvey, E. Newton, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Henderson, Leon, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Bronk Correspondence-I, 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 39)
    - Institute of Aeromedical Sciences, 1942 (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Irving, Laurence, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Bronk Correspondence-J, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 42)
    - Bronk Correspondence-K, 1940-1943 (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Bronk Correspondence-L, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Bronk Correspondence-M, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 45)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Visiting Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 59, Folder 46)
    - Bronk Correspondence-M, 1942-1944 (Box 59, Folder 47)
    - Bronk Correspondence-Mc, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 48)
    - McCulloch, Warren, National Research Council (NRC), 1942-1943 (Box 59, Folder 49)
    - Bronk Correspondence-N, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 50)
    - National Defense Research Committee, 1941-1950 (Box 59, Folder 51)
    - NRC, Committee on Aviation Medicine, 1941-1942 (Box 59, Folder 52)
    - NRC, Motion Sickness and Low Pressure Chambers, 1941-1943 (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Societies, Institutions, Associations, 1946-1948
    - Bronk Correspondence-A, 1946-1948 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Aero Medical Association, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - AAAS, Centennial Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 60, Folder 4)